Guide to the Cornell University College of Engineering Dean's Office records, [ca. 1916-2000]
Cornell University College of Engineering Dean's Office records, [ca. 1916-2000]
- Criteria For Accrediting Programs in Engineering in the USA - Accreditation Board for Engineering and Technology, 1988-1989 (Box 31, Folder 19)
- Correspondence Regarding Doctoral Programs in Engineering, folder 1, 1994-1995 (Box 31, Folder 20)
- Correspondence Regarding Doctoral Programs In Engineering, folder 2, 1994-1995 (Box 31, Folder 21)
- NYS Regents Doctoral Evaluation Project - Self-Study Questionnaire - Doctoral Program Statewide Review - Chemical Engineering, June 1991 (Box 31, Folder 22)
- NYS Regents Doctoral Evaluation Project - Self-Study Questionnaire - Doctoral Program Statewide Review - Civil & Environmental Engineering, June 1991 (Box 31, Folder 23)
- NYS Regents Doctoral Evaluation Project - Self-Study Questionnaire - Doctoral Program Statewide Review - Sibley School of Mechanical and Aerospace Engineering, July 1991 (Box 31, Folder 24)
- NYS Regents Doctoral Evaluation Project - Self-Study Questionnaire - Doctoral Program Statewide Review - Applied & Engineering Physics, July 1991 (Box 31, Folder 25)
- NYS Regents Doctoral Evaluation Project - Self-Study Questionnaire - Doctoral Program Statewide Review - Agricultural and Biological Engineering, folder 1, June 1991 (Box 31, Folder 26)
- NYS Regents Doctoral Evaluation Project - Self-Study Questionnaire - Doctoral Program Statewide Review - Agricultural and Biological Engineering, folder 2, June 1991 (Box 31, Folder 27)
- Nuclear Science & Engineering Doctoral Program Self-Study Report, July 1991 (Box 31, Folder 28)
- Doctoral Program Statewide Review - Agricultural & Biological Engineering Program - College of Agriculture and Life Sciences, Section 3-Index, June 1991 (Box 31, Folder 29)
- Doctoral Program Statewide Review - Agricultural & Biological Engineering Program - College of Agriculture and Life Sciences, Section 4-Appendix, June 1991 (Box 31, Folder 30)
- NYS Regents Doctoral Evaluation Project - School of Civil & Environmental Engineering, June 1991 (Box 31, Folder 31)
- Theoretical and Applied Mechanics Doctoral Program Review (Statewide), July 1991 (Box 31, Folder 32)
- Background on the College of Engineering (Box 31, Folder 33)
- Engineering Legislation Re: Core Curriculum, folder 1, May 1969 (Box 31, Folder 34)
- Engineering Legislation Re: Core Curriculum, folder 2, May 1969 (Box 31, Folder 35)
- Report on the College of Engineering, 1950 (Box 32, Folder 1)
- Information Manual for the College of Engineering, 1983 (Box 32, Folder 2)
- Engineering College Council - Report to the Board of Trustees, 1975-1987 (Box 32, Folder 3)
- Engineering College Council - Report to the Board of Trustees, 1966-1975 (Box 32, Folder 4)
- Engineering College Council - Report to the Board of Trustees, 1955-1966 (Box 32, Folder 5)
- Engineering College Council Membership File, 1987-1997 (Box 32, Folder 6)
- Engineering College Council Membership File, 1937-1987 (Box 32, Folder 7)
- Implantable Active Devices - A Commemoration of 25 Years of Pacing - Wilson Greatbatch, folder 1 (Box 32, Folder 8-9)
- Miscellaneous Newsletters, 1978-1980 (Box 32, Folder 10)
- Quarterly list of Research Proposals Submitted, College of Engineering, 1980, 1983 (Box 32, Folder 11)
- Placement Report, 1979-1982 (Box 32, Folder 12)
- Newsletter - Focus, 1981, 1983 (Box 32, Folder 13)
- Newsletter - College of Engineering, 1980-1983 (Box 32, Folder 14)
- Newsletter - Department of Geological Sciences, 1982-1983 (Box 32, Folder 15)
- Newsletter - School of Operations Research and Industrial Engineering, 1981, 1983-1984 (Box 32, Folder 16)
- Newsletter - School of Applied & Engineering Physics, 1979, 1982, 1984 (Box 32, Folder 17)
- Newsletter - Theoretical & Applied Mechanics, 1979, 1982 (Box 32, Folder 18)
- Newsletter - Prosus, Cornell Program on Submircometer Structures, 1980-1984 (Box 32, Folder 19)
- Newsletter - Engineering Cooperative Program (Box 32, Folder 20)
- Newsletter - School of Electrical Engineering, 1978-1982 (Box 32, Folder 21)
- Newsletter - Sibley School of Mechanical And Aerospace Engineering, 1981 (Box 32, Folder 22)
- Newsletter - Department of Computer Science, 1983 (Box 32, Folder 23)
- Newsletter - School of Chemical Engineering, 1976-1984 (Box 32, Folder 24)
- Newsletter - Materials Science and Engineering, 1979-1985 (Box 32, Folder 25)
- Newsletter - School of Civil and Environmental Engineering, 1979-1984 (Box 32, Folder 26)
- Financial Aid Packages (Box 32, Folder 27)
- Research in Engineering & Applied Sciences - Supplement, 1992 (Box 32, Folder 28)
- Research in Engineering & Applied Sciences - Supplement, 1992 (Box 32, Folder 29)
- Faculty Research Activities, 1982-1983 (Box 32, Folder 30)
- Research in Engineering & Applied Sciences, Summer 1990 (Box 32, Folder 31)
- Research in Engineering & Applied Sciences, Winter 1987 (Box 32, Folder 32)
- Engineering at Cornell (Box 32, Folder 33)
- College of Engineering (Box 32, Folder 34)
- Nuclear Reactor Laboratory (Box 32, Folder 35)
- The Materials and Metallurgy Laboratory at Cornell (Box 32, Folder 36)
- The Master Plan - For Engineering Facilities at Cornell, Summer 1986 (Box 32, Folder 37)
- Engineering Student Handbook, 1989-1990 (Box 32, Folder 38)
- Engineering Student Handbook, 1990-1991 (Box 32, Folder 39)
- The Cornell Ideas (Box 32, Folder 40)
- Graduate Study in Electrical Engineering at Cornell (Box 32, Folder 41)
- Cornell University Announcements - Graduate Study in Engineering and Applied Physics (Box 32, Folder 42)
- Engineering Students Handbook, 1991-1992 (Box 32, Folder 43)
- Submicron Research (Box 32, Folder 44)
- College of Engineering (Box 32, Folder 45)
- Charter, 1936-1986 (Box 32, Folder 46)
- Cornell Engineer, Spring 1984 (Box 32, Folder 47)
- Cornell Engineer, Spring 1984 (Box 32, Folder 48)
- Cornell Engineer, Fall 1984 (Box 32, Folder 49)
- Cornell Engineer, Spring 1985 (Box 32, Folder 50)
- Cornell Engineer, Spring 1985 (Box 32, Folder 51)
- Cornell Engineer, 1986 (Box 32, Folder 52)
- Cornell Engineer, 1986 (Box 32, Folder 53)
- Cornell Geology Through the Years (Box 32, Folder 54)
- Applied and Engineering Physics at Cornell (Box 32, Folder 55)
- Accreditation Board for Engineering and Technology - Questionnaire for Review of Engineering Programs - Volume II - Chemical Engineering, June 1986 (Box 33, Folder 1)
- Accreditation Board for Engineering and Technology - Questionnaire for Review of Engineering Programs - Volume I, June 1980 (Box 33, Folder 2)
- Accreditation Board for Engineering and Technology - Questionnaire for Review of Engineering Programs - Volume I, June 1983 (Box 33, Folder 3)
- Accreditation Board for Engineering and Technology - Questionnaire for Review of Engineering Programs - Volume II - Engineering Physics, June 1986 (Box 33, Folder 4)
- Accreditation Board for Engineering and Technology - Volume II - Self-Study Questionnaire for Review of Engineering Programs - Materials Science and Engineering, folder 1, June 1989 (Box 33, Folder 5)
- Accreditation Board for Engineering and Technology - Volume II - Self-Study Questionnaire for Review of Engineering Programs - Materials Science and Engineering, folder 2, June 1989 (Box 33, Folder 6)
- Accreditation Board for Engineering and Technology - Volume II - Self-Study Questionnaire for Review of Engineering Programs - Civil Engineering, folder 1, June 1989 (Box 33, Folder 7)
- Accreditation Board for Engineering and Technology - Volume II - Self-Study Questionnaire for Review of Engineering Programs - Civil Engineering, folder 2, June 1989 (Box 33, Folder 8)
- Accreditation Board for Engineering and Technology - Questionnaire for Review of Engineering Programs - Volume II - Mechanical Engineering, 1986 (Box 33, Folder 9)
- Accreditation Board for Engineering and Technology - Questionnaire for Review of Engineering Programs - Volume II - Materials Science & Engineering, 1986 (Box 33, Folder 10)
- Accreditation Board for Engineering and Technology - Questionnaire for Review of Engineering Programs - Volume II - Civil Engineering, folder 1, 1986 (Box 33, Folder 11)
- Accreditation Board for Engineering and Technology - Questionnaire for Review of Engineering Programs - Volume II - Civil Engineering, folder 2, 1986 (Box 33, Folder 12)
- Accreditation Board for Engineering and Technology - Questionnaire for Review of Engineering Programs - Volume I, 1986 (Box 33, Folder 13)
- Accreditation Board for Engineering and Technology - Volume I - Self-Study Questionnaire for Review of Engineering Programs, folder 1, June 1989 (Box 33, Folder 14)
- Accreditation Board for Engineering and Technology - Volume I - Self-Study Questionnaire for Review of Engineering Programs, folder 2, June 1989 (Box 33, Folder 15)
- Accreditation Board for Engineering and Technology - Volume II - Self-Study Questionnaire for Review of Engineering Programs - Applied and Engineering Physics, June 1989 (Box 33, Folder 16)
- Accreditation Board for Engineering and Technology - Volume II - Self-Study Questionnaire for Review of Engineering Programs - Operations Research and Engineering, folder 1, June 1989 (Box 33, Folder 17)
- Accreditation Board for Engineering and Technology - Volume II - Self-Study Questionnaire for Review of Engineering Programs - Operations Research and Engineering, folder 2, June 1989 (Box 33, Folder 18)
- Accreditation Board for Engineering and Technology - Volume II - Self-Study Questionnaire for Review of Engineering Programs - Mechanical Engineering, folder 1, June 1989 (Box 33, Folder 19)
- Accreditation Board for Engineering and Technology - Volume II - Self-Study Questionnaire for Review of Engineering Programs - Mechanical Engineering, folder 2, June 1989 (Box 33, Folder 20)
- Accreditation Board for Engineering and Technology - Volume II - Self-Study Questionnaire for Review of Engineering Programs - Agricultural Engineering, folder 1, October 1986 (Box 33, Folder 21)
- Accreditation Board for Engineering and Technology - Volume II - Self-Study Questionnaire for Review of Engineering Programs - Agricultural Engineering, folder 2, October 1986 (Box 33, Folder 22)
- Cornell Center for Advanced Technology - Biotechnology - Executive Committee, May, 8, 1996 (Box 33, Folder 23)
- Correspondence & General Regarding Dean Edmund T. Cranch, folder 1, 1951-1978 (Box 33, Folder 24)
- Correspondence & General Regarding Dean Edmund T. Cranch, folder 2, 1951-1978 (Box 33, Folder 25)
- Correspondence & General Regarding Dean Edmund T. Cranch, folder 3, 1951-1978 (Box 33, Folder 26)
- Engineers' Council for Professional Development - Accreditation Inspections, folder II, 1963-1968 (Box 33, Folder 27)
- Engineers' Council for Professional Development - Accreditation Inspections, folder III, 1963-1968 (Box 33, Folder 28)
- Engineers' Council For Professional Development - Accreditation Team for Cornell, folder 1, 1969 (Box 33, Folder 29)
- Engineers' Council for Professional Development - Accreditation Inspections, folder I, 1963-1968 (Box 33, Folder 30)
- Engineers' Council For Professional Development - Accreditation Team for Cornell, folder 2, Spring 1994 (Box 33, Folder 31)
- Engineering College Advisory Council, folder 1, Spring 1994 (Box 33, Folder 32)
- Engineering College Advisory Council, folder 2, Spring 1994 (Box 33, Folder 33)
- Engineering College Advisory Council, folder 3, Spring 1994 (Box 33, Folder 34)
- Engineering College Advisory Council, folder 1, Fall 1994 (Box 34, Folder 1)
- Engineering College Advisory Council Meeting, folder 2, Fall 1994 (Box 34, Folder 2)
- Engineering College Advisory Council Meeting, folder 1, Spring 1995 (Box 34, Folder 3)
- Engineering College Advisory Council Meeting, folder 2, Spring 1995 (Box 34, Folder 4)
- Engineering College Advisory Council, Spring 1996 (Box 34, Folder 5)
- Engineering College Advisory Council, Fall 1996 (Box 34, Folder 6)
- Engineering College Advisory Council Meeting, Spring 1997 (Box 34, Folder 7)
- Engineering College Advisory Council Meeting - External Reviews, Spring 1997 (Box 34, Folder 8)
- Engineering College Advisory Council Meeting - Notes, Spring 1997 (Box 34, Folder 9)
- Engineering College Advisory Council Meeting - "College Evaluation" Talk, Spring 1997 (Box 34, Folder 10)
- Engineers' Council for Professional Development - Review of Engineering Programs - Electrical Engineering, folder 1, 1980 (Box 34, Folder 11)
- Engineers' Council for Professional Development - Review of Engineering Programs - Electrical Engineering, folder 2, 1980 (Box 34, Folder 12)
- Engineers' Council for Professional Development - Review of Engineering Programs - Electrical Engineering, folder 3, 1980 (Box 34, Folder 13)
- Engineers' Council for Professional Development - Review of Engineering Programs - Electrical Engineering, folder 4, 1980 (Box 34, Folder 14)
- Engineers' Council for Professional Development - Volume II - Questionnaire for Review of Engineering Programs - Theoretical & Applied Mechanics, 1980 (Box 34, Folder 15)
- Engineers' Council for Professional Development - Volume II - Questionnaire for Review of Engineering Programs - Materials Science & Engineering, folder 1, 1980 (Box 34, Folder 16)
- Engineers' Council for Professional Development - Volume II - Questionnaire for Review of Engineering Programs - Materials Science & Engineering, folder 2, 1980 (Box 34, Folder 17)
- Engineers' Council for Professional Development - Volume II - Questionnaire for Review of Engineering Programs - Mechanical Engineering, folder 1, 1980 (Box 34, Folder 18)
- Engineers' Council for Professional Development - Volume II - Questionnaire for Review of Engineering Programs - Mechanical Engineering, folder 2, 1980 (Box 34, Folder 19)
- Engineers' Council for Professional Development - Volume II - Questionnaire for Review of Engineering Programs - Mechanical Engineering, folder 3, 1980 (Box 34, Folder 20)
- Engineers' Council for Professional Development - Review of Engineering Programs - Applied & Engineering Physics, 1980 (Box 34, Folder 21)
- Engineers' Council for Professional Development - Review of Engineering Programs - Civil Engineering, folder 1, 1980 (Box 34, Folder 22)
- Engineers' Council for Professional Development - Review of Engineering Programs - Civil Engineering, folder 2, 1980 (Box 34, Folder 23)
- Engineers' Council for Professional Development - Review of Engineering Programs - Chemical Engineering, 1980 (Box 34, Folder 24)
- Engineers' Council for Professional Development - Review of Engineering Programs - Agricultural Engineering, folder 1, 1980 (Box 34, Folder 25)
- Engineers' Council for Professional Development - Review of Engineering Programs - Agricultural Engineering, folder 2, 1980 (Box 34, Folder 26)
- Engineers' Council for Professional Development - Review of Engineering Programs - Aerospace Engineering, 1980 (Box 34, Folder 27)
- Engineers' Council for Professional Development - Review of Engineering Programs - Engineering School, 1980 (Box 34, Folder 28)
- Engineers' Council for Professional Development - Volume II - Questionnaire for Review of Engineering Programs - Operations Research & Industrial Engineering, 1980 (Box 34, Folder 29)
- College Curriculum Governing Board, folder 1, 1993-1994 (Box 34, Folder 30)
- College Curriculum Governing Board, folder 2, 1993-1994 (Box 34, Folder 31)
- College Curriculum Governing Board, 1994-1995 (Box 34, Folder 32)
- Diversity in Engineering (Box 35, Folder 1)
- Search for Director of Computing, 1979 (Box 35, Folder 2)
- AD HOC Planning Group for Engineering Facilities, folder 1, 1984-1985 (Box 35, Folder 3)
- AD HOC Planning Group for Engineering Facilities, folder 2, 1984-1985 (Box 35, Folder 4)
- AD HOC Planning Group for Engineering Facilities, folder 3, 1984-1985 (Box 35, Folder 5)
- AD HOC Planning Group for Engineering Facilities, folder 1, 1984 (Box 35, Folder 6)
- AD HOC Planning Group for Engineering Facilities, folder 2, 1984 (Box 35, Folder 7)
- AD HOC Planning Group for Engineering Facilities, folder 1, 1984 (Box 35, Folder 8)
- Faculty Salaries - AD HOC Committee Report, 1953-1979 (Box 35, Folder 9)
- Facilities Committee (R.N. White Chairman), 1986-1989 (Box 35, Folder 10)
- Correspondence Regarding Professor L.M. Falkson, 1965-1966 (Box 35, Folder 11)
- Ford Social Fellowship, 1971-1974 (Box 35, Folder 12)
- French Exchange Program, 1968-1985 (Box 35, Folder 13)
- French Exchange Program - Ecole Polytechnique, 1984-1985 (Box 35, Folder 14)
- French Exchange Program - Agreement with Ecole Centrale De Lyon - Ecully, France, folder 1, 1983-1989 (Box 35, Folder 15)
- French Exchange Program - Agreement with Ecole Centrale De Lyon - Ecully, France, folder 2, 1983-1989 (Box 35, Folder 16)
- French Exchange Program - Agreement with Ecole Centrale De Lyon - Ecully, France, folder 3, 1983-1989 (Box 35, Folder 17)
- French Exchange Program - Agreement with Ecole Centrale Des Arts et Manufactures, folder 1, 1984-1988 (Box 35, Folder 18)
- French Exchange Program - Agreement with Ecole Centrale Des Arts et Manufactures, folder 2, 1984-1988 (Box 35, Folder 19)
- FYI Notes, folder 1, 1994 (Box 35, Folder 20)
- FYI Notes, folder 2, 1994 (Box 35, Folder 21)
- FYI Notes, folder 1, 1995 (Box 35, Folder 22)
- FYI Notes, folder 2, 1995 (Box 35, Folder 23)
- FYI Notes, folder 3, 1995 (Box 35, Folder 24)
- Geological Sciences Building, folder 1, 1981-1985 (Box 35, Folder 25)
- Geological Sciences Building, folder 2, 1981-1985 (Box 35, Folder 26)
- Geological Sciences Building, folder 3, 1981-1985 (Box 35, Folder 27)
- Geological Sciences - Proposals, folder 1, 1971-1983 (Box 35, Folder 28)
- Geological Sciences - Proposals, folder 2, 1971-1983 (Box 35, Folder 29)
- Geological Sciences - Proposals, folder 3, 1971-1983 (Box 35, Folder 30)
- Geological Sciences - Proposals, folder 4, 1971-1983 (Box 35, Folder 31)
- Geological Sciences - Department of Cornell-Harvard-Yale Summer Field Camp, 1981-1982 (Box 35, Folder 32)
- Geological Sciences - Degree Program, 1974-1975 (Box 35, Folder 33)
- Gifford, P.W. - Gifford-Hill, 1979-1983 (Box 35, Folder 34)
- Gifts Disposition Pending, folder 1, 1984-1990 (Box 35, Folder 35)
- Gifts Disposition Pending, folder 2, 1984-1990 (Box 35, Folder 36)
- Gifts Disposition Pending, folder 3, 1984-1990 (Box 35, Folder 37)
- Glenmede Trust Company, 1980-1987 (Box 36, Folder 1-2)
- Cornell Center for the Study of Global Change, 1986-1987 (Box 36, Folder 3)
- Goals, Priorities & Plans for the Next Five Years- Cornell in the 1970's; goals of engineering (Box 36, Folder 4-5)
- U.S. & State Government- Bills etc., 1984-1987 (Box 36, Folder 6-8)
- Grading Trends, 1979-1983 (Box 36, Folder 9)
- Graduate Engineering Data- Questionnaire- University of Wisconsin, 1979-1980 (Box 36, Folder 10)
- Graduate Students, 1964-1984 (Box 36, Folder 11-14)
- Graduate School, 1982-1987 (Box 36, Folder 15-18)
- Graduate Student Financial Support, 1991-1992 (Box 36, Folder 19)
- Graduate Student Financial Support, 1992-1997 (Box 36, Folder 20)
- Solomon Cady Hollister Papers- 1904- [1915-1982] (Box 36, Folder 21-22)
- Cornell 1996-1999, Joint Services Electronics Program- Proposal Review, Oct. 1995 (Box 36, Folder 23-24)
- Cornell University Law School, 1974-1982 (Box 36, Folder 25)
- Leal, Gary, 1985 (Box 36, Folder 26)
- Learning Skills Center, 1973-1983 (Box 36, Folder 27)
- Learning Skills Center, 1973-1983 (Box 36, Folder 28)
- Legal Liability of Faculty (Box 36, Folder 29)
- Lynn, Walter R., 1966-1984 (Box 36, Folder 30-31)
- General Correspondence Ma-Mi, 1966-1967 (Box 36, Folder 32)
- General Correspondence Ma-Mi, 1966-1967 (Box 37, Folder 1)
- General Correspondence Ml, 1964-1981 (Box 37, Folder 2-3)
- General Correspondence Mo-Mu, 1967-1969 (Box 37, Folder 4)
- General Correspondence Mo-Mu, 1967-1969 (Box 37, Folder 5)
- Manufacturing Systems Engineering, 1984 (Box 37, Folder 6)
- Masters of Engineering- Intern Program, 1984-1988 (Box 37, Folder 7)
- Masters of Engineering Proposals, 1973-1988 (Box 37, Folder 8)
- Materials Science Center, July 1983 (Box 37, Folder 9-10)
- Materials Science Center By-Laws, 1987-1970 (Box 37, Folder 11)
- Materials Science Industrial Affiliates Program, 1984-1989 (Box 37, Folder 12)
- McGill University, 1971-1972 (Box 37, Folder 13)
- Merrill Presidential Scholars, 1984-1989 (Box 37, Folder 14-15)
- Correspondence Regarding Medical College, 1973-1984 (Box 37, Folder 16)
- Mearl Corporation, 1985-1989 (Box 37, Folder 17)
- Minority Office- MYSEAT Program- Cornell Young Scholars Programs, 1988-1989 (Box 37, Folder 18)
- Minority Office- MYSEAT Program- Cornell Young Scholars Programs, 1988-1989 (Box 37, Folder 19)
- Minority Educational Affairs/COSEP- College Plan Study Committee, 1983-1987 (Box 37, Folder 20-21)
- Correspondence regarding Professor Robert P. Merrill (Box 37, Folder 22)
- Merrill Presidential Scholars, 1984-1989 (Box 37, Folder 23)
- Minorities- Graduate Education- "GEM Program" (Box 37, Folder 24)
- Minorities- Graduate Education- "GEM Program" (Box 37, Folder 25)
- Minorities- Graduate Education- "GEM Program" (Box 37, Folder 26)
- Dedication of Submicron Facility, October 16-17, 1981 (Box 37, Folder 27)
- Dedication of Submicron Facility- Lester Knights involvement, October 16-17, 1981 (Box 37, Folder 28)
- Dedication of Submicron Facility- comments afterwards, October 16-17, 1981 (Box 37, Folder 29)
- Dedication of Submicron Facility- photographs, October 16-17, 1981 (Box 37, Folder 30)
- Dedication of Submicron Facility, October 16-17, 1981 (Box 37, Folder 31)
- Dedication of Submicron Facility- publicity & press releases, October 16-17, 1981 (Box 37, Folder 32)
- Submicron Structures Facility- Director's Search, October 16-17, 1981 (Box 37, Folder 33)
- Dedication of Submicron Facility- Research Highlights, October 16-17, 1981 (Box 37, Folder 34)
- Mogami Geotechnical Lab Dedication, September 29, 1989 (Box 37, Folder 35)
- Dedication of Submicron Facility- Re: Social arrangements, hotels etc., October 16-17, 1981 (Box 37, Folder 36)
- Dedication of Submicron Facility- Regrets to invitation, October 16-17, 1981 (Box 37, Folder 37)
- General Correspondence- N, 1972-1988 (Box 37, Folder 38)
- National Association of State Universities and Land Grant Colleges, 1966-1989 (Box 38, Folder 1-2)
- National Research Council, 1974-1986 (Box 38, Folder 3-4)
- National Research & Resource Facility for Submicron Structures (NRRFSS), 1985-1987 (Box 38, Folder 5-7)
- National Science Foundation General, July 1, 1985-1989 (Box 38, Folder 8)
- National Science Foundation- Engineering Research Centers, 1984-1987 (Box 38, Folder 9-10)
- National Science Foundation- Research & Instructional Equipment Grants, 1975-1980 (Box 38, Folder 11)
- Networking, Computer, 1983 (Box 38, Folder 12)
- NYS Science and Technology Foundation, 1961-1989 (Box 38, Folder 13)
- Northeast Utilities, 1982-1983 (Box 38, Folder 14)
- NRRFSS Policy Board (Box 38, Folder 15-16)
- Nuclear Regulatory Commission, 1977-1989 (Box 38, Folder 17-19)
- Olin Hall Renovation, 1984-1986 (Box 38, Folder 20-21)
- Olin Hall Renovation, 1986-1988 (Box 38, Folder 22-23)
- College of Engineering Orientation, 1980-1988 (Box 38, Folder 24)
- Other Foreign Universities & Institutes, 1979 (Box 38, Folder 25)
- Owens-Corning Fiberglass, 1966-1985 (Box 38, Folder 26)
- General Correspondence P, 1972-1981 (Box 38, Folder 27)
- Perkin-Elmer Corporation, 1980-1985 (Box 38, Folder 28)
- Personal Computers (PC's), 1983-1984 (Box 38, Folder 29)
- Phillipson, Warren, 1983 (Box 39, Folder 1)
- Phone Message Notes, March-September 1994 (Box 39, Folder 2)
- Phone Message Notes, July 1993-April 1994 (Box 39, Folder 3)
- Lab for Plasma Studies- Steering Committee, 1972-1975 (Box 39, Folder 4-5)
- Polaroid Corporation, 1983-1988 (Box 39, Folder 6)
- Priorities for the Future of Engineering, Spring 1984 (Box 39, Folder 7)